And that brings this class on LangChain,
Chat with Your Data, to an end.
In this class, we've covered how to use
LangChain to load data
from a variety of
document sources using LangChain's 80-plus
different document
loaders.
From there,
we split the documents into chunks,
and talk about a lot of the nuances
that arrive when doing so.
After that, we take those chunks,
create embeddings for them,
and put them into a vector store,
showing how that
easily enables semantic search.
But we also talk about some of the
downsides of semantic search,
and where it can fail in
the certain edge cases that arise.
The next thing that
we cover is retrieval,
maybe my favorite part of the class,
where we talk about a lot of new
and advanced and really
fun retrieval algorithms for
overcoming those edge cases.
We combine that with
LLMs in the next session,
where we take
those retrieved documents,
we take the user question,
we pass it to an LLM,
and we generate an
answer to the original question.
But there's
still one thing missing, which
is the conversational
aspect of it.
And that's
where we finish out the class, by
creating a fully functioning end-to-end chatbot
over your data.
I've
really enjoyed teaching this class. I
hope you guys have enjoyed taking it.
And I want to thank everyone in the
open source who has
contributed a lot of
the things that make
this class possible,
like all the prompts and a lot of
the functionality that you see.
As you guys build
with LangChain and discover
new ways of doing
things and new tips and techniques,
I hope that you share what you'll
learn on Twitter or even open
up a PR in LangChain. It's a
really fast-moving field, and it's an
exciting time.
I really look forward
to seeing how you
apply everything that you
learned in this class.